她是女主角  又是我的女朋友
Okay, she is the star of the play, and she is my girlfriend.
我在跟这部戏里的女主角上床
I get to have sex with the star of the play.
别人都听见了  我知道
People can hear you. I know.
她很漂亮吧  对吧
Wow, she looks great, doesn't she? Mm.
嗨   嗨
Hi. Hi.
那个男的可真帅
That is one good-looking man.
是我眼花  还是他的腹肌真的露出来了
Is it just me, or can you actually see his abs through his overcoat?
那  你做这行很久了吗
So, you been doing this long?
没有  你是我的第一个  把钱放在桌上
No. You're my first. Put the money on the table.
很好啊
Oh, yeah.
啊哦  好舒服
Ooh, that's nice.
不会吧
Dude.
这上衣很贵吗  你说贵就贵
Is that an expensive blouse? If you want it to be.
你女朋友的钮扣
Here's your girlfriend's button.
老友记  第四季  第13集  瑞秋坠入情网
Friends S04E13  The One With Rachel's Crush
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
你还留着中学时的旧衣服嘛
Oh, hey, Mon, do you still have, like, your old blouses and dresses from high school?
我想应该还有几件  怎么了
Yeah, I think I have some around here somewhere. Why?
孕妇装都卖的好贵
Well, it's just maternity clothes are so expensive.
瑞秋  你卧室那边  我收拾了一堆你的东西
Hey, Rach, I made a pile of your stuff on this side of your room.
看你要不要
If you could just... Ugh!
拿皮包扔它
Throw your purses at it.
布鲁明戴尔裁减了我的部门
Bloomingdale's eliminated my department.
天哪  你失业了吗  没有  但我被塞到专人采购部
Oh, my God. Are you out of a job? No, they stuck me in Personal Shopping...
比原来矮了一大截
...which is just a huge step down.
专人采购部  是做什么
Personal Shopping, what is that?
陪有钱人逛街
Like where you walk around with snooty rich people...
帮他们挑衣服
...and tell them what to buy?
听起来好棒
Uh-huh. That sounds great.
嘿
Hey.
对不起  我们好像换过公寓了吧
Um, excuse me, we switched apartments.
你再也不能吃我们的东西了  吃白食的好日子结束了
You can't eat our food anymore. That gravy train has ended.
吃白食
There's gravy?
你们房子大  就得随时准备应付人来人往
If you have the big apartment, then deal with people coming over all the time.
所以冰箱要塞满东西  对面那个才是你们的房子
That fridge has got to be stocked, okay? That's your apartment now.
你在干什么  我留了个甜甜圈在这里
What are you doing? I think I left a doughnut up here.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
凯西的戏怎样
Oh, how was Kathy's play?
凯西半裸演床戏
Well, Kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex...
跟一个大帅哥
...with a real good-looking guy.
这就像有人把我的恶梦写成戏
Yeah, it was like somebody wrote down my worst nightmare...
还要我花上32块钱去看
...and then charged me $32 to see it.
这个点子有赚头
That's a good idea for a business.
我受不了了  他们会在台上夜夜打得火热
I'm totally screwed, okay? They're gonna be hot and heavy on-stage every night...
然后去参加剧组派对  会设法中伤我
...and then they're gonna go to their cast parties, and he's gonna undermine me.
像是 "你男朋友呢  他叫什么钱斯特吗"
You know, he'll be like, "So where's your boyfriend? What's his name, Chester?"
她会说 "不  不  不  是钱德"  他就说“随便啦”
And she'll go, "No, no, no. It's Chandler." He'll go, "Whatever. Ha-ha-ha."
这招不错
That is a good trick.
看么  我该怎么办
All right, look, look. What am I gonna do?
钱德  他们是演员  他们只是在工作
Chandler, look, they're actors. They're there to do a job.
工作总要逢场作戏  但不是都会弄假成真的
Just because they work together doesn't mean they'll get together.
就像苏珊莎兰登和提姆罗宾斯也会那样做
Just because it happened with Susan Sarandon and Tim Robbins...
并不代表你的女友也会和别人做
...doesn't mean it's gonna happen with them.
还有  亚历鲍德温和金贝辛格
Oh, oh. Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
汤姆克鲁斯和妮可基德曼
Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman. Yeah.
梅尔杰布森和克林伊斯威特
Okay, Mel Gibson and Clint Eastwood.
他们不是一对
They're not a couple.
喔  我听懂了
Oh, okay, I get the game now.
好  我问你个问题
Okay, look, look. Let me ask you a question.
他们在台上演床戏时  真的很火热吗
When they were doing it on-stage, was it like really hot?
对啊
Huh. Oh, yeah.
那就没问题了
Well, okay, so then you're fine.
如果两个演员私底下在一起
Look, the rule is when two actors are actually doing it off-stage...
他们之间的火花就会消失
...then all the sexual tension between them is gone.
只要台上很火热  你就不用担心
Okay? So as long as it's hot on-stage, you got nothing to worry about.
台上没有了火热度  你就有麻烦了
It's when the heat goes away, that's when you're in trouble.
真的吗
Really?
你们看过我演的每出戏
You guys have been to every play I've been in.
我有在台上擦出过火花吗
Have I ever had chemistry on-stage?
没有  对吧
No. No.
你晚上要陪我去看戏吗
So, uh, man, are you gonna go see the play with me tonight?
我不知道  看你女朋友
You know what? I don't know how comfortable I am...
跟别人亲热  我觉得很尴尬
...going to see how hot the sex is between some guy and your girlfriend.
我知道  但是  不  我人在现场
Yeah, I know... No, no, no, oh, I'm there.
嘿  嘿  摩妮卡
Hey. Hey, Mon.
要煎饼吗   你做煎饼了
Want some pancakes? You made pancakes?
对  拿个盘子
Yep. Grab a plate.
不  不  别过来
No, no. Stay right there.
越来越近了
Getting closer.
放心
Don't worry...
也有谷月  松糕  松饼
...we also have cereals, muffins, waffles...
果酱  果肉酱和果皮酱  其实是同一种东西
...and jams, jellies and marmalades, which I'm fairly certain are the same thing.
星期六要看球赛   欢迎加入
Also we're watching the game here Saturday, if people want to come over.
好啊
Oh, yeah.Oh.
我正想找你们到对面看球
I was having people over for the game.
是吗  谁跟谁比
Oh, yeah? Who's playing?
球员跟球员
The players.
有人在怀念当女主人喔
Somebody seems to be missing being the hostess.
拜托   我不知道有多轻松
Ha, ha. Please, it's a relief, is what it is, is what it is.
好  菲比  盘子准备好
All right. Pheebs, stick out your plate.
哦
Oh.
摩妮卡  我要辞职
Monica, I'm quitting.
我帮一个老女人塞上丁字裤  结果她也没买
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong, and she didn't even buy it.
我告诉你  我要辞职  现在就要跟老板说
I'm telling you, I'm quitting, that's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
我要  我要  我要
Yes, I am. Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
好  拜拜  听到留言请回电
Okay, bye. Call me when you get this message.
华森先生  我有事找你
Oh! Mr. Waltham? I, uh, really need to talk to you.
等一下  我忙得不可开交
In a moment, please. I'm in the middle of a task.
你有顾客上门
And you have a customer.
你好  你好  我是约书亚
Hi. Hi. I'm Joshua.
我是瑞秋葛林  有什么需要   约书亚
Hi, I'm Rachel Green. What can I do for you, Joshua?
我的衣服都要重买  我老婆  我的前妻
Well, I need a new wardrobe. My wife... Well, my ex-wife...
噢  我真遗憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.
她把我的衣服都烧了
Anyway, she burned all of my clothes.
我救回两件  这套西装和一条裙子
So I got away with two things: This suit and what turned out to be a, uh, skirt. Heh.
起码这套西装还好看
Well, at least that's a great suit.
但是穿着裙子 拿这套去干洗店一点也不好玩
Yeah, it wasn't much fun dropping it off at the dry cleaners in the skirt.
所以  我需要包括内衣裤全套
So I need everything down to underwear.
如果你愿意  我整个人就交给你了
So if you're willing, I'm, uh... I'm all yours.
好的
Okay.
瑞秋  你有事找我
Rachel, you needed to speak to me?
没有了  不是我
No, no, that wasn't me.
那我们走吧  带你去看我的内衣
Well, we should get started. Let me show you my underwear.
我们的内衣专柜
The selection of underwear that we carry.
对不起  是这边  这边  抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry. It's this way.It's this way? Sorry.
对吧  现在他们之间一点感觉也没有
I'm right, right? There was, like, no chemistry between them.
之前他们有热度  而现在却不见了
Before, they had heat. And now there's no heat.
你知道其中含意  乔伊说过
Now, you know what this means. Joey told us what this means.
先别急着下定论  行吗
Let's not jump to any conclusions, all right?
他们之间还是有一点点火花的
There was some sexual chemistry between them.
拜托  根本就像表兄妹在做爱
Oh, come on. It was like cousins having sex up there.
她来了  什么都别说  冷静  跟平常一样
Here she comes. Don't say a word, okay? Just be cool. Don't be, you know, you.
你们好   嘿
Hey, you guys. Hey.
谢谢你们又来了
Oh, thank you so much for coming again.
你喜欢吗  那当然
Did you like it tonight? Absolutely.
尼克点不着火柴时  好搞笑啊
Wasn't Nick funny when he couldn't get his match lit?
这是一出好戏吧  对吧
It's a good play, isn't it? Mm.
我很喜欢  你演得很棒
I loved the play. Uh, yeah, you were great.
尼克也是
And, uh, Nick, ditto.
很明显  你在跟他做爱
Clearly, you're having sex with him.
好
Okay.
很明显  我在跟他做爱
Clearly, I'm having sex with him?
拜托  太明显了  你们之间没有任何火花
Oh, come on. It was so obvious. There was no chemistry between you two.
好的  让我先搞清楚
Okay, let me just get this straight.
你先指责我不忠  又侮辱我的演技
You're accusing me of cheating on you, and you're insulting my performance?
当然啊  这也难怪我能看到
You know, I can see how this could happen.
你们每天晚上都光着身体  爱抚  热吻
You know, you're up there every night, naked, touching, kissing.
那是演戏啊  钱德  这是我的工作
Acting. Chandler, this is my job.
这是剧中场景  我是在演戏  你怎么可以不相信我
I'm playing a part in a play. How can you not trust me?
你应该明白  我们就是这样开始的
Well, you can understand, given how we started.
你居然拿这个来攻击我
I can't believe you're throwing that in my face.
事实如此  你刚才也没否认
Well, that is what happened, and I don't even see you denying this.
够了  等你长成熟了再来找我
I'll tell you what, Chandler. Why don't you call me when you grow up?
好啊  那你可有得时间等了
Yeah, well, don't expect that to happen any time soon.
噢  我的工作最棒了
Oh, I have the best job in the entire world.
来了个最帅的帅哥
The most adorable guy came over today...
我整天都在打扮他
...and I got to dress him up all day.
瑞秋有新的洋娃娃了
Rachel has a new doll.
真希望他是  我会把他跟瑞秋娃娃凑在一起
Oh, I wish he was a doll. Then I could get a Rachel doll and bump them together...
让它们玩亲亲游戏
...and make kissing noises.
他的名字最好听了  以前我都不觉得  约书亚
Oh, and he's got the most beautiful name. I never realized. Joshua.
约书…亚
Oh, Joshua.
约书亚  约书…
Joshua, Josh.
哈罗
Uh, hello?
嗨
Hi.
什么味道
Ooh, what do I smell?
不知道  但闻起来好香啊
I don't know, but it smells good.
热腾腾的饼干  刚出炉的
Fresh cookies. Hot from the oven. Ooh!
请用  真好  请
Please have some. Oh, yo.
我只是在这里闲着  随便弄了一些好吃的
I've just been fiddling around in here, making delicious treats for everyone.
新的《花花公子》
Wow. The new Playboy.
我随手买的
Yeah, just something I picked up.
饼干和黄色书刊  好棒的妈妈
Cookies and porn? You're the best mom ever.
什么
What? What?
没什么  约书亚对V字领有些看法  现场听才好玩
Nothing, it's just something Joshua said about V-necks, but you had to be there.
杰森穿V字领  好看吗
How does, uh, Jason look in a V-neck?
是约书亚  随便啦
It's Joshua. Oh, whatever.
等等  那不是要拿走的
Wait. Wait. This isn't takeout.
讨厌吃饱了就要跑  拜托  别走
Well, hate to eat and run. No, wait, please don't go.
也有女生看的黄色杂志
I've got porn for you too.
我不需要
Yeah, I don't need it.
大家应该呆在这里
People are supposed to want to hang out here.
为什么  亲爱的  有什么大不了的
Why? Honey, what is the big deal?
我是女主人
I'm the hostess.
不是那些臭男生  我一直都是女主人
Not those guys. I'm always the hostess.
连小的时候  别的女生都会带着她们的新娃娃到我的舞会
I mean, even when I was little, the girls brought their dollies to my tea party.
我能提供最好的氛围
I served the best air.
那你干嘛让大家烦恼
Why did you make a whole big thing...
叫大家去大的地方
...out of everyone has to hang out in the big apartment?
我想惩罚他们  因为抢走了我们的公寓
'Cause they took our apartment, I wanted to punish them.
我惩罚完了  他们也吃到苦头了
But I'm done now. They've suffered enough.
要惩罚他们  就该把他们关在外面
If you wanted to punish them, you should have just made them hang out here.
那倒是
Yeah, that's true.
我一定会让这里比对面好十倍
All right then, when I'm done with this place, it's gonna be ten times better than that place!
我们要捣毁对面吗
Oh, are we gonna trash their place?
台阶
Steps.
贱人
Slut.
你们一定很乐于听到   凯西在跟那个人上床
You'll all be very happy to hear that Kathy is sleeping with that guy.
真的  你猜对了
What? So you were right?
我当面问她  她并没有否认
I confronted her, and she didn't deny it.
我不住这里
I don't live here.
钱德  她怎么说的
Chandler. Chandler, what did she say?
等等   你确定吗
Wait a minute. Come here.are you sure?
我也许是醉了  但我听得懂她的话
Well, I may be drunk, but I know what she said.
所以我跑去朱理牛排
So then I went over to Beefsteak Chewley's...
查理牛排   对
Beefsteak Charlie's? Yes.
你和我总是
See, you and I have always been like:
哎哟
Oops.
嘿  需要帮忙吗  不用了
Hey, do you need help with that? No, I got it.
我感觉好糟  从没这样空虚过
Oh, I just feel bad. I never vacuum.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
今天我和约书亚在一起1小时了  他还没约我出去
So I was with Joshua for an hour today, and he has not asked me out.
真让人灰心  那你就约他嘛
It's so frustrating. Why don't you ask him out?
没错  感觉会很刺激
Oh, yeah. Totally. That's such a turn-on.
真的  看起来感觉不会很饥渴吗
Really? It doesn't seem desperate?
那样才刺激
Ooh, that's the turn-on.
他刚离婚  跟女人相处可能会紧张
He just got a divorce, right? So he's probably really nervous around women.
你就先主动嘛  迈出你的第一步
You know? Maybe you just need to make the first move.
我以前从没约过男生出去  你没约过男生出去
I've never asked a guy out before. You've never asked a guy out?
没有  你呢
No, have you?
上千次了吧
Thousands of times. Ha, ha.
这也不是什么光荣的事  对吧
That doesn't make me sound too good, does it?
我都不知道该怎么去做
I don't even know how I would go about it.
我会从头到尾打量一个女人  然后说
Oh, what I do is, uh, I look a woman up and down and I say:
嘿
"Hey.
"你在做什么"
How you doing?"
拜托
Oh, please.
嘿
Hey.
你要怎样做
How you doing?
好  我也这样做
You know what? I'm gonna do that.
现在就打电话约他  约他出来
I'm gonna call him up and I'm gonna ask him out.
好  有什么难的   约就约
Yeah. I can do that. Ask him out.
你好吗
"How you doing?"
喂  约书亚
Hi, Joshua?
瑞秋葛林  布鲁明戴尔的
It's Rachel Green, from Bloomingdale's.
对了  我想问你是不是
Yeah, um, I was just wondering if you, um...
是不是
If you, um...
今天在店里掉了皮夹
Left your wallet at the store today?
我们捡到一个皮夹  我们
Oh, well, we found a wallet, and we...
那驾驶证  好主意
The license? Oh, that is a good idea.
嗯   让我看看   驾照是一位
Uh, well, let's see. This license belongs to a, uh...
叫菲比先生的
Uh, belongs to a Mr. Pheebs.
对
And, um, yeah.
抱歉打扰你了  明天见  拜拜
So okay. So sorry to bother you at home. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
你做过几千次了  我从没做过
You've done that a thousand times? I've never done that.
天呐  我只是担心他不答应
Oh, God, I just got so nervous that he was gonna say no.
你得让他无法拒绝  就像  尼克队的球票
Well, you gotta give him something he can't say no too, like, uh, Knicks tickets.
约他去看尼克队的比赛  他一定会答应
Invite the guy to a Knicks game. You're guaranteed he'll say yes.
你觉得有用  绝对的  不行  我去行吗
Really? You think that will work? Absolutely! And if it doesn't, can I get the extra ticket?
什么声音
What the heck is that?
她有打来吗
Did she call?
没有  抱歉
No. Sorry.
也许我应该打给她  不要
Well, maybe I should call her. No.
忘了她吧  你不需要她的  不必这样啊
Forget her, man. You don't need her. Don't need that.
没错  她的所作所为让人无法原谅
He's right. What she did was unforgivable.
对啊  但你要知道  假如是我错了呢
Well, yeah, but you know, what if I was wrong?
你怎么会错的
How might you be wrong?
要是她没跟那个人上床呢
Well, you know, what if she didn't actually sleep with the guy?
大哥  告诉我这是她跟你说的
Dude, tell me she actually told you this.
她没有  是我看了她的戏感觉他们之间毫无火花
She did not have to tell me. I saw the play and there was no heat.
罗斯  帮我说句话  你就根据这个
Back me up here, Ross. That's all your basing this on?
这不是在帮我
That's not backing me up.
你说过私底下如果有热情
You said, you know, with the off-stage and the heat...
在台上表演就会没有
...and the on-stage and the heat... Whoa, whoa.
那只是个理论  很多理论都行不通的
That was just a theory. There's a lot of theories that didn't pan out.
孤枪侠  共产主义  几何学
Lone gunman, communism, geometry.
天哪
Oh, my God.
约书亚  你要不要去看篮球
"Joshua, Would you like to go to a basketball game with..."
篮球  真有意思  我正好有票
"You know, it's funny, basketball, because I happen to have tickets to..."
谁喜欢尼克队啊
"Who likes the Knicks?"
你觉得如何
What do you think? Oh.
哎  作为一个单身的女人来说…
Well, as a single woman, who is available...
我觉得你看起来很帅
...I think you look great.
是吗  没错
Huh. Yeah? Yup.
真的  帅呆了
Oh, yeah, you look great.
这样看起来还真配
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this looks great.
你喜欢吗
Um, so you like it?
对  很喜欢  实际上  我是想在家里穿的
I do, I do. I love it. In fact, I think I'm gonna wear it home.
太好了  谢谢你的帮助
Great. Well, thank you so much for all your help.
我想是的   那就这样
Well, I guess, uh... I guess this is it. Yeah.
谢了
Thanks.
或许我春天再过来  找你买泳衣
Maybe I'll see you in the spring with the... For the bathing suits.
你不现在买吗
You don't want to do that now?
不买了  改天见
Oh, that's okay.
希望常常能看到你
Anyway, hopefully I'll see you around sometime.
篮球
Basketball.
什么
Sorry?
我…
I, uh...
有两张今晚尼克队比赛的球票  如果你感兴趣
I have two tickets to the Knicks game tonight if you're interested...
谢谢你这星期的惠顾
...just as a thank-you for this week.
哇  太棒了
Wow. That would be great.
真的  对啊  那会很精彩的
Really? Yeah, That would be fantastic.
我外甥最迷尼克队了
My nephew is crazy about the Knicks.
太棒了  谢谢你  瑞秋
This is fantastic. Thank you so much, Rachel.
早安  你好
Good morning. Hi.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我只想来跟你说声对不起
Hey. I just, I just wanted to come over to-to say that I'm sorry.
我真是世上最笨最笨的白痴了
You know, I acted like the biggest idiot in the world.
我完全明白你为什么这么伤心
And I can completely understand why you were so upset.
我希望你给我打电话
I really wish you'd called me.
我知道  我也很后悔
Yeah, I know. I wish I had too.
不过我觉得这是好事  对吧
But, you know, I think this is a good thing. You know?
我们吵了第一次架  现在关系有进展了
Because we've had our first fight, and now we can move on.
至少我确定  我知道的  但是
You know, I mean, I know for me, but...
尼克的裤子
Nick's pants?
对
Yeah.
那好
Yeah. Well.
看来第二次更大的吵架又要继续了
I think our second fight is going to be a big one.
好  下次你会怎么说  "我有一张多余的门票"
Okay, for next time, what do you say? "I have an extra ticket."
"一张多余的门票" 而不是 "两张"  "我有一张多余的门票"
"An extra ticket." Not "two tickets." I have and extra ticket.
你第一次约男生出去  就被拒绝
So the first time you asked a guy out he turned you down?
他并没有拒绝我   他参加比赛了
He didn't turn me down. He's at the game, isn't he?
我约到他了  只是我没去
I got the date. I'm just not on it.
都弄好了
Okay, it's ready.
来吧  什么弄好了
Come on. What's ready?
过来就知道了
Just come.
哇哦  我的天哪
Oh, my God.
哇  莫妮卡  好漂亮喔
Wow. Monica, this is beautiful.
你整整忙了两天
Oh, did you work for two days straight?
差不多
Pretty much.
这个地板好不好
So, what do you think of the floor?
我不知道  看起来一样的
I don't know. Looks the same.
以前是铺的地毯
You used to have carpet.
对喔
Oh, yeah.
我做了点心
So I made snacks.
你们随便坐
Please, just hang out, okay?
我要稍微休息一下眼睛
I'm just gonna rest my eyes for just a little bit.
要我们待会儿再来吗
Mon, do you want us to come back later?
不  不用  留下来吧  你们继续聊天
Oh, no, no, no. Stay, stay, stay. Just keep talking.
我一直都是女主人
I'm always the hostess.
嘿  怎么样
Hey. How'd it go?
还好  她之前没跟他上床
So? Well, she wasn't sleeping with him.
太好了  现在有了
Oh, good. She is now.
你在说什么  我在说她是个恶女人
What are you saying? I'm saying that she is a devil woman.
你认识她这么个人
You think you know a person...
才一转身  就跑回去跟尼克上床
...then they turn around and they sleep with Nick.
尼克和他的大胸肌  还有他的大咪咪
Nick and his rock-hard pecs and his giant man-nipples.
我恨他  我也恨她
I hate him. And I hate her.
我不恨她  我爱她  都是我的错  真的
Well, I don't hate her. I love her. This is all my fault, really.
不会吧  怎么会是你的错
Oh. How? How is it your fault?
因为我该给她打电话的
Because, ugh, I should have called.
要是吵完后我马上打给她  她就不会跟尼克出去约会了
You know, if I'd just called her, she never would have gone out with Nick...
他们也就不会上床了
...and they wouldn't have ended up in bed together.
是我亲手把她送给他了
I threw her at his man-nipples.
宝贝  这不是你的错
Honey, this is not your fault.
就算吵架  她也不该跟别人上床
Just because you guys had a fight does not justify her sleeping with someone.
除非她以为你们分手了
Well, if she thought they were on a break...
瑞秋  你的客人掉了皮夹  约书亚伯格
Rachel, one of your customers seems to have left his billfold. A Joshua Burgen.
真的  你会通知他吗
Really? Will you call him?
好  没问题
Yes, I will. Absolutely.
哈罗   瑞秋
Hello, Rachel.
嗨   约书亚
Hi, Joshua.
我是故意留下皮夹的
I left my wallet here on purpose.
真的
Really?
我只是想再见到你
Yes, I just wanted to see you again.
我很高兴
Oh, I'm glad.
瑞秋  我有话要对你说
Rachel, I'd like to say something to you.
什么
Yes?
你好吗
How you doing?